https://www.danforthpewter.com/privacy_policy/

JewelryEarringsPost EarringsWire EarringsMini Wire EarringsNecklacesNecklacesMini NecklacesCorded NecklacesBraceletsAccessoriesBarrettesZipper pullsScatter Pins & BroochesPurse mirrorsMoney ClipsCufflinksCharmsKeyringsOrnaments & HolidaysOrnamentsAnnual OrnamentsBird OrnamentsClassic Ornaments12 Days of Christmas OrnamentsBaby OrnamentsWildlife OrnamentsOrnament CollectionsSmall Tree DecorationsNativityParty Favor GiftsCollectionsDecoratingClover, Green, & CelticValentine's DayMother's DayFather's DayGraduationLightingOil LampsCandlesticks & CandleholdersAdventLighting AccessoriesSmall WondersPocket Coins & TokensNetsukesMilagrosPalm StonesMagnetsBaby & KidsKeyringsSpecial OffersSaleRetiringPewter Points Reward ProgramPromotionsWish ListGift Cards
Account
Home
Privacy Policy
PRIVACY POLICY
Privacy policy for Danforth Pewterers LLC and our website; www.danforthpewter.com. Thank you for visiting our website. Updated August 19, 2020
We Respect Your Privacy
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
When you visit our site, we do not collect your name, e-mail address, or any other personal information unless you give it to us.
If you choose to share your contact information with us, we will use your information to get back to you regarding the reason you contacted us. Unless you ask us not to, we may email or snail mail you to tell you about specials and new products or services. We may also share your information with other companies who have products we think you may like. At any time, you can opt-out of having your information shared by emailing that request to info@danforthpewter.com.
Registration
In order to become a member on our website, you complete the registration form and create a password. During registration, you enter certain information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact you about the products/services you're interested in.
E-mail Addresses
We collect email addresses through our optional email sign up form and from our online order entry form, from telephone orders, catalog requests and forms filled out on social media platforms.
If you give us your email address, we may email you about a completed or incomplete order, or to tell you about our products and services and special offers. We will also use your email address to notify you of the status of your online order. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, you can opt-out here info@danforthpewter.com.
Postal Addresses
We collect postal addresses that you give us through our optional catalog request. We also collect postal addresses from online and telephone orders, as well as forms filled out on social media. If you have given us your postal address, we may mail you about new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not want to receive mailings from us, please contact customer service by phone or email. Also, you may receive mailings from other reputable companies who may send you offers and information they think will be valuable to you. You can, however, have your name put on our "do not share" list.  At any time you can opt-out of having your information shared by emailing that request to info@danforthpewter.com.
Telephone Numbers
We keep phone numbers for the sole purpose of contacting individuals when we have a question or need more information regarding your order. We do not trade, rent, or sell telephone numbers to any other parties.
Orders
When you order from us, you give us contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used only for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we'll use this information to contact you. All information regarding your Danforth Pewter order is kept confidential.
Site Statistics
We share aggregated demographic information with our partners. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. We collect statistics about our sales, traffic patterns, and related site information. The information we collect about all visitors to our website includes the visitor's browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. We also collect potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. You may opt-out of this practice by visiting Google Analytics' currently available opt-outs page.
Security
When you use your credit card to shop at danforthpewter.com, rest assured that the transaction is secure. Our servers use Secure Socket Layer (SSL), an advanced encryption technology. This technology safeguards your personal information and guarantees privacy.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (e.g. billing or customer service) have access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Cookies
We use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance their experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.
Links
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
Surveys & Contests
From time to time, we invite you to participate in surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used to monitor or improve the experience of using this site.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 1-800-222-3142 or via email at info@danforthpewter.com.
© Copyright 2019 Danforth Pewter. All Rights Reserved.
